# **SAWARNEE SETHI**

1227, RANI BAGH, DELHI - 110034 · (91) 7042725575 · SAWARNEE1997@GMAIL.COM

I am a Computer Science Engineering student, constantly learning different technologies and upgrading myself. I am good in software and web development and have made many projects using different technologies. Apart from the development, I am also good in communication (spoken and written) and possess good leadership qualities. I am good in representing something effectively and love to take part in challenges and hackathons. I want to be an entrepreneur and I think that work exposure and experience gained during this time will help me a lot to achieve my dream.





### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER INTERN**

AIRPORTS AUTHORITY OF INDIA

I am developing a seperate web portal for monitoring of different projects (initiated, under development, and completed) at different Indian Airports.

June 2018 - July 2018

### **WEB DESIGN INTERN**

**ARBUNIZE** 

I reviewed and edit front end codes of the main website of the company - getboarded.com

December 2017 - March 2018

# **EDUCATION**

### **BHAGWAN PARSHURAM INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (IPU)**

**B.TECH** 

Computer Science Engineering Percentage: 81%

August 2015 - May 2019

### D.L.D.A.V MODEL SCHOOL, PITAMPURA

HIGHER SECONDAY EDUCATION (12TH)

Central Board of Secondary Education Percentage: 92.5%

2014 - 2015

### D.L.D.A.V MODEL SCHOOL, PITAMPURA

MATRICULATION (10TH)

Central Board of Secondary Education CGPA: 9.6

2012 - 2013

# **SKILLS**

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TOOLS



















- ✓ Full Stack Web Development
- ✓ Java & J2EE
- ✓ DBMS (SQL Databases)
- ✓ Software Development

### **PROJECTS**

#### WEB PORTAL FOR MONITORING OF DIFFERENT PROJECTS AT DIFFERENT INDIAN AIRPORTS

AIRPORTS AUTHORITY OF INDIA

I am developing a seperate web portal for monitoring of different projects (initiated, under development, and completed) at different Indian Airports.

**Under Development** 

### **ONLINE REGISTRATION SYSTEM**

A complete web application through which students can store their confidentials such as marksheets and other information online and in response, they will receive a qr code. They have to show this qr code to the operator at the time of admission and on scanning this code, operator will obtain all the files and information on his system and he can manage them in any order he needs. This project also inlude Forget Password and QR code generator modules.

Click to view video of running project

View on Github

# **INTERESTS**

Apart from being a web developer, I enjoy most of my time being outdoors. I enjoy outdoor adventures and hanging out with friends.

When forced indoors, I follow a number of sci-fi and fantasy genre movies and television shows, I like to play guitar and video games, and I spend a large amount of my free time exploring the latest technology advancements in different fields.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- ❤ Won gold medal in badminton(singles and doubles) for 2 consecutive years at College Annual sports meet.
- ▼ Coordinated a complete sports event(badminton) at the College Annual sports meet.